Inventory of David D. Laitin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed Matter, 1951-2007 (Box 12-23)
  - Halgan (The Struggle), Vol. 1, No. 1, United Liberation Front of Western Somalia (ULFWS), 1979 January (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - History of Western Somalia: A Concise Analytical Survey, United Liberation Front of Western Somalia (ULFWS), undated (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - U.N. Chronicle, "Somalia: UNOSOM Withdrawal Completed Virtually Without a Hitch,", 1995 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - "Conference on the Somali Remittance Sector," United Nations Development Program (UNDP), 2003 December 3-4 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - "Basic Education for Nomads: Reports of a Seminar Held in Mogadishu, Somalia," UNESCO/UNICEF Co-operative Program, 1978 April 1-9 (Box-folder 22: 12)
  - "Report of the Independent Expert on the Situation of Human Rights in Somalia, Ghanim Alnajjar," U.N. Economic and Social Council, 2005 March 11 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - U.N. General Assembly Sessions, 1977 October (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - U.N. General Assembly Sessions, 1978 September-October (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - "Somalia," press release, U.N. Security Council, 2005 July (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - "The Trust Territories of Somaliland Under Italian Administration," United Nations Technical Assistance Program, 1952 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - "Situation Report No. 16: Somalia," U.S. Agency for International Development (U.S. A.I.D.), 1992 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - "Somalia," U.S. Congress Sub-Committee on Africa, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - U.S. Department of State (Office of the Assistant Secretary Spokesman), Stockholm, Sweden, 1992 December 14 (Box-folder 23: 5)
  - U.S. Institute of Peace Journal, 1993 (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - U.S. Institute of Peace Journal, "Removing Barricades in Somalia: Options for Peace and Rehabilitation," Adam, Hussein, Ford, Richard, et al., 1978 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - U.S. Mission to the U.N. press release, 1992 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Various clippings, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - The Washington Quarterly, "The Intervention Dilemma," Blechman, Barry M., 1995 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - The Washington Quarterly, "The U.S. and the U.N. in Somalia: The Limits of Intervention," Howe, Jonathan H., 1995 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - West Africa, "Voices of the Ogaden,", 1978 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Halgan (The Struggle), Western Somali Liberation Front (WSLF), 1978-1983 (Box-folder 23: 13)
    Includes issues from October 31, 1978; May 20 and October 10, 1982; and February 20, 1983.
  - Western Somali Liberation Front (WSLF) press release, undated (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - Background to the Liberation Struggle and Go From My Country: Western Somalia and Abyssinian Colonialism, 1978 (Box-folder 23: 15)
    Two publications about Western Somalia.
  - Westview Press bibliography, undated (Box-folder 23: 16)
  - Tables From the Data Files of the World Bank, "Somalia,", 1989-1990 (Box-folder 23: 17)
  - World Policy Journal, "The Humanitarian Trap," Rieff, David, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 23: 18)
  - World Today, "Somalia: From Humanitarian Intervention to Military Offensive?," Makinda, Samuel M., 1993 (Box-folder 23: 19)
  - Xisaab: Fasalka Saddexaad ee Dugsiga Sare, 1979 (Box-folder 23: 20)